{
    "Subj_Name":"Data Structure & Algorithms",
    "Quiz_Details":"Algorithms",
    "Quiz_No":"Quiz 4",
    "Quiz_Questions":[
        {
            "question":"It is a list of instructions specifying a precise description of a step by step process that terminates after a finite number of steps for solving an algorithm problem producing the correct answer in the end",
            "answer":["Algorithm","Algorithms"]
        },{
            "question":"It is a recipe for solving problems. ",
            "answer":["Algorithm","Algorithms"]
        },{
            "question":"A finite set of an instruction that specifies a sequence of operation to be carried out in order to solve a specific problem.",
            "answer":["Algorithm","Algorithms"]
        },{
            "question":"An unambiguous procedure specifying a finite number of steps to be taken",
            "answer":["Algorithm","Algorithms"]
        },{
            "question":"______ - there is an exact number of steps to be taken and has an end.",
            "answer":["Finiteness"]
        },{
            "question":"True or False:<br>Absence of Castro - means that every instruction is precisely described and clearly specified",
            "answer":["false"]
        },{
            "question":"________ - Instructions are performed from top to bottom.",
            "answer":["Sequence of Execution"]
        },{
            "question":"________ - defined the unknowns of the problem is specified and with the expected outcome.",
            "answer":["Input and Output","Input Output"]
        },{
            "question":"________ - the solution prescribed is guaranteed to give a correct answer and that the specified process is faithfully carried out.",
            "answer":["Effectiveness"]
        },{
            "question":"_________ - applies to a specific problem or class of problem",
            "answer":["Scope Definition"]
        },{
            "question":"Specifies the steps of algorithm using essentially natural language of superimposed control structure.",
            "answer":["Pseudocode"]
        },{
            "question":"A traditional graphical tool with standardized symbols. Show the sequence of steps in an algorithm",
            "answer":["Flowchart"]
        },{
            "question":"True or False:<br>The flowchart should flow from top to bottom",
            "answer":["True"]
        },{
            "question":"True or False:<br>If the chart becomes complex, utilize connecting blocks",
            "answer":["True"]
        },{
            "question":"True or False:<br>Avoid intersecting flow lines",
            "answer":["True"]
        },{
            "question":"True or False:<br>Use meaningful description in the symbol",
            "answer":["True"]
        },{
            "question":"This flowchart is a formalized graphic representation of a logic sequence, work or manufacturing process, organization chart, or similar formalized structure.",
            "answer":["System Flowchart"]
        },{
            "question":"This flowchart is a graphical representation of a computer program in relation to its sequence of functions",
            "answer":["Program Flowchart"]
        },{
            "question":"Bonus Question. Pogi si jerbee?",
            "answer":["true","yes","pogi","gwapo","cute","oo","oo naman","yes na yes"]
        }
    ]
}
